When he turns up the heat ... they will turn on each other.
The Steam Experiment is a crime, drama, thriller
film directed by Philippe Martinez.
A deranged scientist locks 6 people in a steam room and threatens to turn up the heat
if the local paper doesn't publish his story about global warming.
Jimmy, played by Val Kilmer.
Detective Mancini, played by Armand Assante.
Grant, played by Eric Roberts.
Catherine, played by Megan Brown.
Christopher, played by Patrick Muldoon.
Margaret, played by Cordelia Reynolds.
The Chaos Experiment (previously known as The Steam Experiment) is a 2009 independent suspense thriller
directed by Philippe Martinez and starring Val Kilmer, Armand Assante, and Eric Roberts.
The tone is emotional and intense.